http://www.ucg.ca/about/privacy-policy

Donate
We use cookies on this site to enhance your user experience.
By clicking any link on this page you are giving your consent for us to set cookies. More Info
OK, I agree
Decline
Privacy Policy
Introduction
The privacy of your personal information is important to the United Church of God-Canada. This Privacy Policy discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. We also provide instructions on how to update or remove personal information you have supplied to us.
Information You Provide to Us
Requesting literature for you or a friend: You provide the following information: name, postal address and email.
Information We Collect
You can visit UCG.ca without sharing your personal information.
We use Google Analytics and cookies in order to improve our website content, user experience and analyze how the website is used. Google Analytics collects information about you and your use of the website whenever you visit. For example, Google Analytics may collect various forms of information such as site traffic statistics, page views, operating system and browser type, and approximate location. If you would like to opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics go to this website for more information: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
We use Bambora to process personal data on our behalf. Bambora processes payments for donations and other secured payments as needed. Visit Bambora’s privacy policy on how this data is protected.
How We Use Information Provided and Collected
Requesting literature for you or a friend: If you supply us with your postal address via our online form, you will only receive the information which you requested. If you provide us with an email address, then you may receive an email notification about your request.
Other ways we may use your information may include, but not limited to: improving the design and content of the website and notifying you of any special announcements.
We do not sell to third parties your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of this website. However, we may use the collected information to integrate with third party service providers to help provide better content or help us to analyze our web stats.
From time to time, we may use website visitor
information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to this website and notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at this website periodically.
Update or Remove Personal Information
Where required by law, we offer you the ability to access the information we have on you. If you believe the information we have on you is incorrect, you can contact us so we can update it and keep your data accurate. If at any point you would like your provided information to be deleted, you can contact us. We will ask for some confirmation of your identity before changing any information.
We intend to retain the personal information provided for only as long as we need it to fulfill the purposes for which it was initially provided.
© 1995-2020 United Church of God-Canada
Reproduction in whole or in part without permission is prohibited. All correspondence and questions should be sent to info@ucg.ca.
Send inquiries regarding the operation of this Web site to webmaster@ucg.ca.
